http://www.safetecvision.co.uk/privacy-policy#cookies

Receive Our Weekly Updates
×
Simply enter your name and email address below to be among the first to receive:
Sign Up
View our full range of products helping to stop the spread of Covid-19   CLICK HERE >
PRIVACY POLICYSafetec Direct LTD (“Safetec Direct LTD”, “we”, “us”, “our”), the data controller, are committed to always protect the privacy and security of our online visitors/customers. We recognise the importance of using this information in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and General Data Protection Regulation.Personal DataWe operate an opt-in policy when obtaining personal details from our customers and site visitors. We may collect the following when you wish to sign up to receive marketing communications on our site, or simply when placing a transaction on the siteNameContact details including billing and delivery addressesCredit card details if applicableWhere we rely on consent to send marketing communications, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time by contacting our customer services department or updating your marketing preferences online or through the unsubscribe link sent through our marketing emails.Payment InformationWe use the payment information given by all customers to ensure no fraudulent activity is taking place against you the customer, and us. This is necessary to ensure Financial Conduct is followed always.We do not store your credit or debit card details on our system but instead process transactions through a secure Payment Service Provider.Purposes for which your personal data is usedWe will use the personal data which you provide to us for the following purposes;Allowing us to process sales ordersTaking payments in relation to the purchase of productsSending you email newslettersUndertaking customer researchUnderstanding how our customers interact with our websites and personalising their repeat visitsDetermining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns and advertisingResponding to queries and complaintsTo comply with legal obligations, as part of our general business operations, and for other business administration purposesTo carry out contractual obligations entered between you and us CookiesWe use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue without changing your settings, we'll assume that you are happy to receive all cookies on our website. You can change your cookie settings at any time through the browser settings.The cookies used on our site are:CookieWhat are they used for?BASKET IDWe store this type of cookie in order to allow you ‘the customer’ to purchase products from our website. Google AnalyticsWe store this cookie so we can gather data on how our customers use our website in order to better improve our website. The cookies collect information based on an anonymous form.ASP.NET_Session IDWe store this cookie because it allows us to recognise your sessions whilst using our website.Atuvc/ atuvsWe store this cookie in order to have the social links on our website. This is treated as basic functionality cookies. What is a cookie?A cookie is a piece of information that is stored by your computer's hard drive by your web browser, which tracks your movements within websites. Most browsers are automatically set to accept cookies, but you can alter the settings of your browser to prevent automatic acceptance, should you wish. Our site uses cookies to keep track of how often you visit our site, the contents of your shopping cart, previous purchases and to deliver content specific to your interests, to assist us in updating our service for our customers’ benefit. If you choose not to receive cookies, you may still use most of the features of our website, including the ability to purchase items. The use of cookies is an industry standard, but should you require any further information regarding the technical specifications, please contact us.Your rightsThe right; to be informed about how your personal information is being usedThe right; to access the personal information we hold about youThe right; to request the correction of inaccurate personal information we hold about you The right; to request that we delete your data, or stop processing it or collecting it, in some circumstances. Once you have given us instruction to delete your data, we will liaise with our partners to ensure your details are deleted from all systems. This can take up to 72 hours to be completed and written communication will take place to confirm. The right; to stop direct marketing messagesThe right; to complain to your data protection regulatorComplaintsWe try to do everything possible to ensure that complaints do not occur, however, if you feel that your complaint is justified, you can do this in the following ways.Email our customer service team at sales@safetecdirect.co.ukIf you wish to talk a member of our customer service team via telephone, this can be done by calling 0345 500 6060How to Disable CookiesChromePlease click here to see how to disable cookies within Google ChromeSafariPlease click here to see how to disable cookies within SafariFirefoxPlease click here to see how to disable cookies within FirefoxInternet ExplorerPlease click here to see how to disable cookies within Google ChromeApple DevicesPlease click here to see how to disable cookies for Safari on an Apple DeviceAndroidPlease click here to see how to disable cookies within the Android Browser
Customer Information
Knowledge Hub
Contact us
Workwear logo service
Sign up to our newsletter for latest offers, news & more
Sign up to our newsletter for latest offers, news & more
Cookie Terms
This site uses cookies to give you the best shopping experience on our site. By continuing to use this site, you agree to accept these cookies.
Click here to view our cookie information.
